armstrongeconomics.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Armstrong Economics

Armstrong Economics / AE Global Solutions, Inc. (hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Company”, or “we”, or “our”) offers this web site (ArmstrongEconomics.com), along with various products and services (including but not limited to live events, conferences, branded content, social media, blog posts, reports, publications, videos, additional websites and membership platforms, collectively referred to as our “Services”). This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we may collect and use different types of personal and behavioral information in order to deliver the Services. We strive for transparency and trust when it comes to protecting your privacy and it’s important to us that you should enjoy using our Services without compromising your privacy in any way. It is important to note, at any time, you have the right to unsubscribe to any of our communications you may have previously opted in to receive, and you may request to access, change or delete your personal information at any time. We are a small team, and you can get in touch directly through the information provided in our “[Contact Us](https://www.armstrongeconomics.com/contact/)” section.

You should read this policy in conjunction with our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.armstrongeconomics.com/about/terms-and-conditions-of-use/) of this website, and its related Services.

Our policies will be updated from time-to-time. Please refer back regularly to keep yourself updated.

This policy applies to “users” and “customers” and “clients” (or “you”) of the Services, including this website, ArmstrongEconomics.com; that is anyone ordering, registering or interacting with any of the Services offered from the Company. This includes event attendees, subscribers, registrants, website users, app users etc.

**Collection and use of your information**

The information you provide us, and that which we gather based on your activity, helps us to deliver more relevant content as well as create a more seamless experience across the Services and channels through which you may access that content and Services.

We collect and store some information about you in order to deliver Services to you (such as your Socrates membership, one or more email subscriptions, or so that you can attend a conference or event we may hold). We DO NOT share any of that information with any other companies or government agencies, unless otherwise compelled to do so by law, or as otherwise necessary to deliver the Services (in example, credit card payment providers and postal or express services when delivering a tangible report or product purchased). We also collect information when you use our Services and further details are provided below.

**Information we collect / you provide us, which we need in order to provide you with our Services**

There is certain personal information that we need in order to provide the Services. Examples of details we collect in order to fullfill the delivery of Services may include the following:

  * Name
  * Postal address (including postcode)
  * Email address
  * Payment details
  * Account preferences (e.g. certain Services and content topics you prefer to receive communication about)

In addition to the above, examples of the details we may collect for our conferences and events may include the following:

  * Job title
  * additional email (e.g. work email)
  * Company
  * Country
  * Industry

We may ask for different information when offering / delivering other Services, such as phone numbers, gender or date of birth, as indicated when you interact with those Services.

**Information we collect through your use of our Services**

When you use any of the digital platforms that are part of our Services (websites, blogs, or desktop or mobile applications, etc) we collect information that helps us to deliver those Services you have chosen, and to improve your experience. This may be done through the use of cookies and other technologies. Examples of the type of information we may collect are:

  * Browser
  * Email Provider
  * The pages you read on our websites and how you got to them
  * Device
  * IP address
  * Internet Connection
  * Location (in some cases)

You can also volunteer to disclose additional information which may not be essential for us to deliver a Service to you. By providing it you help us to ensure we communicate with you in a way that’s most relevant, useful and engaging for you. We may collect and ask for additional information when you order, purchase, register, subscribe or make use of our Services in any way, for example in person, via our marketing campaigns, via phone or mail orders, or our websites.

**Information we receive from third parties**

While we receive anonymous information from third-parties (e.g. traffic to our websites), the only information we receive from third parties about you as an identified individual to us is limited to confirmations of a purchase you made of any of our Services.

**Information we do not track**

We do not track or collect certain sensitive information about you, such as race, religion, ethnicity, or political opinion.

**How we use your information**

We primarily use your information for the purpose of delivering the Services that you have chosen and to personalize our interactions (which may include advertising) with you. For further details about this, and other ways we may use your information, please read the section(s) below.

**We Value your Privacy & Always Have;**

You have the right to ask for us to update, delete or stop processing information we hold about you. We DO NOT sell or rent your information to any other marketing firm or company. However, please note that there are circumstances in which complete erasure of your information or ceasing to process your information will not be possible for operational, legal and business reasons. This may include if you remain a customer for whom we need to provide Services, or if you wish us to no longer contact you for marketing purposes. In this case we may need to retain some of your details securely in order to facilitate this request by, for example, keeping you on a “do not contact” or suppression list. This will be the only purpose for which your data will be used if this is the case.

**Changes to this policy**

From time to time, we may make changes to the privacy policy. This may be in relation to changes in the law, best practice or changes in our services. These changes will be reflected in this statement, so you should check here regularly.

Last update: May, 25 2018
